Heroes aren't born. They're mutated.
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Mutant Mayhem is a animation,
comedy, action film directed by Jeff Rowe.
After years of being sheltered from the human world, the Turtle brothers set out to win the
hearts of New Yorkers and be accepted as normal teenagers through heroic acts.
Their new friend April O'Neil helps them take on a mysterious crime syndicate, but they
soon get in over their heads when an army of mutants is unleashed upon them.
Donatello (voice), played by Micah Abbey.
Michelangelo (voice), played by Shamon Brown Jr..
Leonardo (voice), played by Nicolas Cantu.
Raphael (voice), played by Brady Noon.
April O'Neil (voice), played by Ayo Edebiri.
Cynthia Utrom (voice), played by Maya Rudolph.
Tales of the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles is an American animated
television series developed for the streaming service Paramount+.
Based on the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles characters created by Peter Laird and
Kevin Eastman, it serves as a spin-off of the 2023 film Mutant Mayhem.
The series follows the Turtles as they navigate their dual lives
as both teenagers and heroes in New York City.
Christopher Yost and Alan Wan serve as showrunners.
Micah Abbey, Shamon Brown Jr., Nicolas Cantu, Brady Noon, and Ayo
Edebiri reprise their voice roles from Mutant Mayhem.
During production on the film, its producers Seth Rogen and Evan Goldberg were
granted approval to develop a canon streaming television series.
The series was announced in July 2023, with Yost and Wan
attached as executive producers and showrunners.
It is produced by Nickelodeon Animation Studio and Point Grey
Pictures, and Titmouse provides animation.
The first season of Tales of the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles debuted
on Paramount+ on August 9, 2024, with all 12 episodes.
It received positive reviews from critics.
A second and final season was picked up alongside the first and debuted on December
12, 2025, with the series being officially cancelled a month prior.
The film explores themes of new york city, sibling
relationship, skateboarding, crime fighter, superhero.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.